Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology records, 1900-2017
Cornell University, New York State College of Human Ecology records,
- Series II. Dean's Files
  - B. Francille Firebaugh (1988-1999)
    - 3) Subject Files and Correspondence (box 114 contains computer disks of correspondence (1980-1996)created in WordPerfect formatted for an IBM compatible computer)
      - Enrollment Planning, 1983-1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Enrollments- Planning, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Enrollments- Planning, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Enrollments, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Enrollments, 1984 Back (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Enrollments- Actual vs. Planned, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Enrollments- Department/ Demographic, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Orientation, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Departments and Units Registrar (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Interdepartmental/Non Departmental Courses and Majors (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - City and Regional Planning (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Cornell-In-Washington, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Advising Coordinators, 1982-1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - HEGIS, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - HEGIS, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - HEGIS, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - HEGIS, 1981 Back (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Health Administration Program, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Diploma Change M.P.S.to M.H.A., 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Gerontology and Rural Aging Proposal, 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Application to Establish a Center on Aging in Rural America, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Gerontology, 1989; (For more information concerning gerontology programs see Box 11 in collection #23/2/2817) (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Gerontology, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Gerontology, 1981-1985 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Report of Scholarship and Grant Awards, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Scholarship and Grant Awards, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - Human Service Studies Five Year Review, 1982-03 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - Guidelines for Review of Departmental Programs (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - Theses and Dissertations, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - Academic Integrity, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Academic Integrity, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Academic Situations, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Academic Status Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Adopt-A-Dean Fund, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Affirmative Action, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Affirmative Action- Sub-Committee on Faculty Retention, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 11-13)
      - Affirmative Action- Sub-Committee on Graduate Students, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Affirmative Action- Sub-Committee on Multi-Cultural Environment, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Affirmative Action- Sub-Committee on Undergraduates, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Affirmative Action- Sub-Committee on Undergraduates, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Report of the Ad-Hoc Committee on Undergraduates, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Alumnae Giving at Women's College, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - American Indian Program, 1984-1991 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Amoco Faculty Awards, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Archives, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Dean's Message, 1988-1992 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Annual Report on the Status of Women, American Indians, Asian Americans, Black Americans and Hispanic Americans at Cornell 1991 and NASULGC Annual Meeting (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Asian American Program, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Biology and Society Major, 1987-1997 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Brofenbrenner Life Course Center (BLCC), 1992 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Brofenbrenner Life Course Center (BLCC), 1992 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Brofenbrenner Life Course Center (BLCC), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 33-35)
      - Brofenbrenner Life Course Center (BLCC), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Brofenbrenner Life Course Center (BLCC), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 38-41)
      - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 44)
      - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 45)
      - Budget, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 46)
      - Budget Reduction, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      - Budget Reduction, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 48)
      - Campus Planning, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 49)
      - Capital Campaign, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 50)
      - Capital Campaign Committee Members, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 51)
      - Career Placement, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 52)
      - Career Placement, 1988-1992 (Box 16, Folder 53)
      - Center for the Environment Governing Committee, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 54)
      - Challenge Industries, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 55)
      - Classification Review, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 56)
      - College Commencement, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 57)
      - College Commencement, 1983 and 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 58)
      - College Commencement, 1983, 1987, 1988, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 59)
      - Colleges (CALS, ILR, VET MED, A and S, Johnson School, Hotel, Architecture), 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 60)
      - Colleges (CALS, ILR, VET MED, A and S, Johnson School, Hotel, Architecture), 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 61)
      - Committee on Academic Status (CAS), 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Committee on Social Implications of Science and Technology Report, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Committee on Special Educational Projects (COSEP), 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Communications Study: Alumni Perceptions- Prepared by the Office of Communications Strategies (May 1991); including background material, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Computer-Aided-Design, 1987-1993 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Computer Services, including networking and policy on legal use of software, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Computer Services, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
      - Computer Services, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Conference- "Rethinking Women and Home Economics in the 20th Century", 1991 (Box 17, Folder 9-11)
      - Conference- "Rethinking Women and Home Economics in the 20th Century"- Olin Library Exhibit "Educating Women: The Unique Role of Cornell's College of Home Economics", 1991-10-1991-12 (Box 105, Folder 46)
      - Consumer Economics and Housing Ad Hoc Curriculum Committee, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Consumer Economics and Housing- Faculty and Staff Positions, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Cooperative Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Cooperative Extension- Affordable Housing, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Cooperative Extension- Funding, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Cooperative Extension- Limited Resource Programs, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Cooperative Extension- Multi-Lingual Program, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Cornell International Studies Advisory Council (CISAC), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 19-21)
      - Cornell Research Council (CRC), 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 22-24)
      - Community and Rural Development Institute (CaRDI), 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 25-27)
      - Community and Rural Development Institute (CaRDI), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Cornell Waste Management Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Corporations, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 30-31)
      - Correspondence A-B, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence C-D, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence E-F, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence G-H, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence I-J, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence K-L, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence M, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence N-P, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence Q-R, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence S, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
      - Correspondence T-V, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence W, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence X-Z, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Council of the Creative and Performing Arts, 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Cultural Activities Task Force, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Dean's Wing Staff Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Design and Environmental Analysis, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Design and Environmental Analysis, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Design and Environmental Analysis, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
      - Design and Environmental Analysis- Advanced Housing, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Design and Environmental Analysis- Filling Faculty Positions, 1986-1990 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Donor Recognition Dinners, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Early Childhood Center, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 19-20)
      - Electing Alumni Trustees, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Emeritus Professors, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
      - Enrollment, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Enrollment, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Evening of Excellence, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Faculty/Administrative Policies, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Faculty Research, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Faculty Research Procedures (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Faculty Tenure and Promotions, 1984-1991 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Farm Bill, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Field and International Studies Program, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 33-35)
      - Field and International Studies Program- Community Learning and Service Program (CLASP), 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Field and International Studies Program- Filling Faculty Positions, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Field and International Studies Program- Foreign University Exchange, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - Flemmie Kittrell Fellowship, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Flora Rosa Descendants, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 40)
      - Flora Rose Prize, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - Founders Day, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - Funding, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 43-44)
      - Future of Home Economics (Think Tank), 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - Golden Key National Honor Society, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 46)
      - Graduate Faculty Representatives and Programs, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 47)
      - Graduate Student Costs and Support, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 48)
      - Hatfield Fellows, 1988-1991 (Box 18, Folder 49)
      - Hispanic American Studies Program (HASP), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 50)
      - History of the College, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 51)
      - Home Economics Administrators- NECG8 Committee, 1988-89 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Home Economics Research Sub-Committee (HERS/ESCOP), 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
      - Howard University, 198-1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Human Development and Family Studies, 1986-1992 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Family Life Development Center Advisory Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Family Life Development Center Advisory Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Family Life Development Center Advisory Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Family Life Development Center Apprenticeship, 1990-1993 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Families in the Balance, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Filling Faculty Positions, 1981-1991 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Migrant Program, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Human Development and Family Studies- Project EASE, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Human Ecology Alumni Affairs and Development, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
      - Human Ecology Alumni Association, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Human Ecology Alumni Association, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Human Ecology Council, 1990-1993 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Human Ecology Extension Chair in Family Policy, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Human Ecology Forum, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Human Ecology News, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Human Resources, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Human Services Studies, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Human Service Administration Program, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Human Service Studies- Anti-Drug Abuse Council, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Human Service Studies- Graduate Concerns, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Human Service Studies- Homeless, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Human Service Studies- Masters of Health Administration, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 31-32)
      - Human Service Studies- Sloan Program, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 33-34)
      - Institute for Comparative and Environmental Toxicology (ICET), 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Interagency Coordinating Committee, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - International, 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 37-38)
      - International Agriculture Program (IAP), 1991 (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - International- China Project, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 40-41)
      - International Federation for Home Economics, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      - International- Guatemala, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - International- India, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 44)
      - International- Ireland, Scotland, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - International- Israel, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - International and Regional Alumni Clubs, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 47)
      - International- Malaysia Publications, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 48-49)
      - International- Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities (MUCIA), 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - International Service for National Agriculture Research (ISNAR), 1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - International Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - International- Uganda, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - International- University of Limerick, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - International- University of the Philippines at Los Banos, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - International Einaudi Center, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
      - Kappa Omicron Nu Honor Society, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Karitas, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Majority Task Force on Aging, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Mann Library, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Martha's in MVR Hall, 1983-1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Martha Van Rensselear Descendants, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Martha van Rensselear Hall- Renovation/Space, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Media Services- Administrative Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Messenger Lectures, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Minority Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Mission Statement, 1977, 1978-1989 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Mortar Board Honor Society, 1986-1990 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Nine/Twelve Month Positions, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Nutritional Sciences, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Nutritional Sciences- Ad Hoc Committee on Nutrition Intervention and Policy, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Nutritional Sciences- Cornell Food and Nutrition Policy Program, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 25-26)
      - Nutritional Sciences- State Board for Dietetics and Nutrition, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Nutritional Sciences- World Food Day, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Office of the President, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Office of the Provost, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - Orientation, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - Phi Beta Delta Honor Society, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - Policy- Gifts and Funds, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - Policy and Procedures- Naming Buildings, 1986-1991 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - President's Council of Cornell Women (PCCW), 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - Provost Committee on Economics, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 36-37)
      - Rationale for Name Change, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - Registrar, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - Research Costs, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - Retirement Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 41)
      - Reunion, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 42)
      - Reunion Project Class of 1954 (Box 20, Folder 43)
      - Risk Communication Seminars, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - Rotary International Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 45)
      - Sabbatical Leaves, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 46)
      - Scholarships, 1989-1993 (Box 20, Folder 47)
      - Scholarships, including Jean Warren, Helen Bull, Bill Vandervort, Elise VanBuren Rice, Helen Tompkins, Helen Gifft, Florence Halpern, Mary Purchase, Lewis Ress, Grace Schermerhorn, Bryceson, 1981-1991 (Box 20, Folder 48)
      - Science and Technology, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 49)
      - Sexual Harassment, 1986-1991 (Box 20, Folder 50)
      - Southeast Asia Program (CSEAP), 1989-1992 (Box 20, Folder 51)
      - State University Construction Fund (Mann Library), 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 52)
      - Statutory Deans Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
      - Student and Relatives Deaths, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - SUNY Tuition, 1979-1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Sustainable Agriculture and Natural Resource Management (SANREM), 1992 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Task Force for Working Women, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Textiles and Apparel, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Textiles and Apparel- American Clothing: Identity in Mass Culture Exhibition, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
      - Textiles and Apparel- American Women's Dresses 1780-1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Textiles and Apparel- Costume Collection, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Textiles and Apparel- Costume Collection, 1972-1989 (Box 105, Folder 40)
      - Textiles and Apparel- Faculty Meetings, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Textiles and Apparel- Mary McFadden Exhibition, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Tuition/Financial Aid, 1988-1991 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Undergraduate Education, 1988-1991 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - United States Information Agency, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Women and Philanthropy, 1988-1991 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Visiting Scholars, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
      - Visiting Scholars, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 21-23)
      - Youth at Risk, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 24-26)
      - Youth at Risk, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 27-28)
      - Youth at Risk, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 29-30)
      - Youth at Risk, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 31-32)
      - Youth at Risk, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 33-35)
      - Youth at Risk, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 36-37)
      - Zamorano- Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 38)
      - Academic Integrity Hearing Board, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Admissions (enrollment, academic planning, commencement), 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Affirmative Action, 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - American Home Economics Association (AHEA), 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Albany, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Alumni Department and Development, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Alumni Development- Endowed Chairs, 1992-93 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Alumni Development- Women and Philanthropy, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Alumni Development- Women and Philanthropy, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Architecture, Art and Planning, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Archives (Retention and Disposition), 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Awards and Prizes (Kittrell, Hatfield, Mann Library), 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Bassett Research Institute/Board of international Food and Agriculture Development (BIFADEC), 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Bronfenbrenner Life Course Center-Review, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Capital Campaign, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Consumer Economics and Housing, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - CEH-Time Use Project/Time Symposium (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Center for Real Estate/Center for Manufacturing Enterprise, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - College of Veterinary Medicine, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Committees on Minorities / Multicultural Environment / Visiting Committee / Affirmative Action, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Committee on Special Educational Projects (COSEP), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Computer Services, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Cooperative Extension, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Cooperative Extension- Metropolitan Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Cooperative State Research Service (CSRS), 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Cornell Food and Nutrition Policy Program (CFNPP), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Corporations and Foundations, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (Mother Theresa University, Malaysia, Ghana, Finland, Hada de Slosser, Canada, Beirut University College), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Cindy Noble, The Netherlands), 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (Dean Firebaugh), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 5-12)
      - Councils and Boards, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Department of Environmental Analysis, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Deans/ Chairs/ Retreats, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Division of Nutritional Sciences- United Nations University, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Employee- Work and Family Survey, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Evening of Excellence, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Facilities (Mann Library, Renovations), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Faculty, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Field and International Studies Program (FISP), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Financial Aid (Tuition), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Family Life Development Center, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Family Life Development Center- Hoyt Symposium, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Government Affairs, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Graduate Students and Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Human Development and Family Studies (HDFS), 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - HDFS- Apprenticeship Program, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - History of College, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - History of Home Economics Fellowship, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Home Economics Organizations, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Hotel Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Human Service Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Human Service Studies-Sloan-Social Work, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Human Ecology Awards and Prizes, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Institute for Comparative and Environmental Toxicology, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - International, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Johnson Graduate School, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Kappa Omicron Nu, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Law School, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Literature Program/ Coalition for Diversity, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 19)